Nehad Salah Badea

Senior .net Developer

Nasr City, Egypt

≥ engnehad2020@gmail.com

01093310381 ## 09/07/1991

Egyptian

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/nehad-salah-140b14146/

Education

Faculty of Computers and Information,

Faculty of Computers and Information /Minia University

10/2009 – 06/2012 | Minia, Egypt

Skills

Programming Skills (C#,SQL

Server, Angular 6, Angular JS, Entity frame Work, ADO. Net, . Net , OOP and . net core)

Profile

I Work as .net developer for more than 6 years in Developing and Maintaining windows and Web applications using different technologies like c#,Asp.net, angularjs , HTML, CSS , JavaScript Crystal Reports, MVC ,Angular,.net Core,CMS Project(Umbraco), Sharepoint and Sql server

Certificates

ITI

ITI Diploma for 9months

TOT from ITI Institute for 3 Months

Professional Experience

Senior .Net Developer,

EL-Mazeed & Data-Stars

04/2020 - present | Maadi, Egypt

I participate in developing Web Application for Ministry of Economy and Planning in Saudi Arabia strategy project for 2030 Vision using MVC , SQL ,Code first for dealing with database and layers in solution . We Convert from .net to .net core Project . We Add bot Feature to system (chatbot on primse) We Make unit test Project to test our work. Make Automation test to screen to help QC team to use this Way in test. Test Project performance using JMeter . We work in Web Application Committee forMinistry of Eco

Senior .Net Developer, IT-Blocks

11/2018 – 04/2020 | Nasr City, Egypt
I Worked as Senior .net developer in IT-Blocks I designed and develop apps using MVC, SQL
Server and c# projects(Samaco Project). I worked in HBKU project in Education Industry (for ITWorks Company) using angular and .net core tools for 6 months. I Worked in CMS project using Umbraco tool for Nasr Bank I worked in project for ministry of Antiquities using MVC, SQL server. I act as team lead in some projects and guide other developers and we try to use agile methodology in our work not waterfall methodology

.Net Developer, NIT Company

11/2014 – 10/2018 | Nasr City, Egypt I Work as .net developer for 4 years in Developing and Maintaining windows and Web applications using different technologies like c#,Asp.net, angularjs , HTML, CSS , JavaScript Crystal Reports and MVC

Courses

PMP

10/2016 - 10/2018 | Nasr City, Cairo